hsbcusa.com 2012-11-30

# Online privacy practices | HSBC

### Online Privacy Practices

Our website offers you the opportunity to view your current account information and make payments online, in addition to providing general information about our company and products. You may also view our Privacy Notice when you visit our website.

To help us learn which products, services and sections of our websites interest you, and to improve your experience, we use "cookies." Cookies are small files that our web server places on your hard drive to track activity on the website during a browsing session, and across multiple sessions. We also use cookies to "remember" which online service you last logged into, so that we can pre-select that service on your next visit.

If you use the Mobile Personal Banking service, we use cookies to determine if you have accepted the Mobile Personal Banking Terms and Conditions. These cookies are small files that our web server places on your mobile device. The cookies we set contain no personal information. These HSBC Cookies only identify that you have accepted the Mobile Personal Banking Terms and Conditions, and cannot be read by any non-HSBC websites.

The cookies we set contain no personal information. HSBC Cookies can only track activity on our website or your acceptance of the Terms and Conditions within Mobile Personal Banking, and cannot be read by any non-HSBC websites.

If you use our EasyView service or other online aggregation services, we collect information about the accounts and relationships included in your EasyView service, including registration information such as your name and e-mail address. We also collect information about the accounts you have designated for the EasyView service, such as account balances, transactions, transaction histories, e-mail information, bills, payment history and other account activity.

We will not disclose any information about you we obtain solely through EasyView to any Non-Affiliate, except as needed to provide your EasyView service, or as required or permitted by law.

We may use this information to offer you other HSBC products and services that may be beneficial to you.

We may also use online profiling to help us better understand your individual financial needs. This information does not identify you personally unless you voluntarily give us personal information while online.

We use third party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and 1x1 pixel.gif (web beacon) technology to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our website and other websites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, their cookie, and IP address. They do not collect personally identifying information. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes. Information about your visits to this and other Web sites may be used to provide ads about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice or to opt-out of these cookies, please visit the [Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "Go to Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool page \(Opens new window\)").

In order to develop our website in line with customer needs we work with WebTrends to track usage on our website. WebTrends provide us with statistics to show us which pages on our website are visited most frequently and how long visitors spend on our site. We use this information to help us plan how we should improve the site.

WebTrends uses a cookie to track the number of unique users of the site. It basically tells us whether we have a small number of regular visitors to the site or a large number of infrequent visitors. None of the information can be traced to an individual - we do not know who you are as a unique user, merely that there are a certain number of people using the site. You should refer to the [WebTrends On Demand Privacy Policy](http://webtrends.com/privacy-policy/ "Go to WebTrends On Demand Privacy Policy page \(Opens new window\)") to learn how they collect and use information.

Last Revised: October, 2012
